YUMI HEO

yumi930330@gmail.com | 07769 666189 https://www.linkedin.com/in/yumi-h/

PROFILE

I am currently studying MSc Data Science at City, University of London. With 4 years of professional experience in the film licensing and distribution business and an additional 8 months of experience in compliance at a fintech, I am eager to board on new business, enhance decision-making processes and support innovation within the business.

KEY SKILLS

• Technical Skills: Python (NumPy, Pandas, matplotlib, seaborn, scikit-learn, PyTorch, PySpark), Matlab, Tableau, PostgreSQL, MS Office (Excel, Word, PowerPoint), Experience in using Github

EDUCATION

City, University of London MSc Data Science

Sep 2023 - Present

- Key modules: Machine Learning (Distinction), Visual Analytics (Distinction), Neural Computing, Big Data, Natural Language Processing, Computer Vision
- Positions of responsibility: Student Voice Ambassador Providing feedback on general experience on campus and encouraging other students to take part in surveys

Dongguk University, Seoul, South Korea BA Economics and English & English Literature

Mar 2015 - Feb 2018

- Key modules: Financial Economics, International Finance, Economics of Information, Post-modernism and Digital Humanities
- Upper second-class honours
- Transferred from Hansung University and started Year 3 to pursue a degree in Economics

Hansung University, Seoul, South Korea English & English Literature

Mar 2013 - Feb 2015

- Key modules: English Syntax, Introduction to English Linguistics
- Completed Year 2 with first-class honours
- Transferred to Dongguk University

WORK EXPERIENCE

SentBe, Seoul, South Korea P/T KYC assistant

Nov 2022 - Aug 2023

- Sentbe is a startup specialising in overseas outbound or inbound remittance services
- Collaborated with Quality Assurance team and Customer Service team to manage the continuous influx of 200+ customers' identities during peak times for overseas remittances
- Monitored identity verification to diminish fraudulent identities and outbound transactions toward more than 25 countries, especially in Asia, Europe and North America

Danal Entertainment, Gyeonggi-do, South Korea Acquisition & Distribution Assistant Manager

Apr 2019 - Oct 2022

- Danal Entertainment is an entertainment company which distributes films, TV shows and music to the platform in
 South Koroa
- Interacted 200+ companies in Korea, the US, the UK, France, Germany, China and Japan to collect information on new video content and negotiate its price with film or TV show sales companies
- Analysed and forecasted sales of obtained 2000+ content and each gross profit from VOD platforms using Excel
 and Google spreadsheet
- Achieved up to 45% recoup for the license fee of a certain film through strategic promotion and communication with platforms such as Netflix, Google Play, Naver serieson, etc. in South Korea

Watcha, Seoul, South Korea P/T Video and Subtitle QC

Dec 2018 - Apr 2019

- Watcha is one of the VOD platforms in South Korea.
- Cooperated with operation team to launch 30+ new films and 10+ TV series every Thursday
- Corrected errors between characters' dialogue and subtitle time, completing at least 4+ TV series per week

NK contents, South Korea Acquisition Assistant

Mar 2018 - Nov 2018

- NK contents is a film and TV show distribution company in South Korea specializing in Japanese films.
- Negotiated with 50+ film sales companies in Japan, the US, the UK, India and France to acquire the film licenses
- Reported on 10+ new scripts of films to follow up on new projects in film markets, working as a team by dividing new scripts or projects by sales companies